

const questions = [
    {
      question: "What is JavaScript primarily used for?",
      options: ["Styling web pages", "Building interactive websites", "Creating databases", "Server-side scripting"],
      correctAnswer: "Building interactive websites",
    },
    {
      question: "Which keyword is used to declare a block-scoped variable in JavaScript?",
      options: ["var", "let", "const", "declare"],
      correctAnswer: "let",
    },
    {
      question: "How do you add an event listener to a button with the id 'myButton' in JavaScript?",
      options: ["document.getElementById('myButton').onEvent('click', myFunction)", "myButton.addEventListener('click', myFunction)", "myButton.click(myFunction)", "addEvent(myButton, 'click', myFunction)"],
      correctAnswer: "myButton.addEventListener('click', myFunction)",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'const' keyword in JavaScript?",
      options: ["To declare a constant variable", "To create a function", "To define a class", "To import external libraries"],
      correctAnswer: "To declare a constant variable",
    },
    {
      question: "Where is the recommended place to include your external JavaScript file in an HTML document?",
      options: ["At the beginning of the <body> section", "Inside the <head> section", "Before the closing </body> tag", "Anywhere in the document"],
      correctAnswer: "Before the closing </body> tag",
    },
    {
      question: "What does the 'NaN' in JavaScript stand for?",
      options: ["Not a Number", "Negative and Null", "New and Null", "None and Number"],
      correctAnswer: "Not a Number",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a falsy value in JavaScript?",
      options: ["null", "undefined", "0", "All of the above"],
      correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
      question: "What method is used to change the content of an HTML element with the id 'myElement'?",
      options: ["changeContent()", "updateHTML()", "document.getElementById('myElement').innerHTML = 'new content'", "setInnerContent('myElement', 'new content')"],
      correctAnswer: "document.getElementById('myElement').innerHTML = 'new content'",
    },
    {
      question: "In JavaScript, what is the purpose of the 'return' statement in a function?",
      options: ["To stop the execution of the function", "To specify the output of the function", "To declare a variable", "To define a loop"],
      correctAnswer: "To specify the output of the function",
    },
    {
      question: "Which symbol is used for single-line comments in JavaScript?",
      options: ["#", "//", "--", "/*"],
      correctAnswer: "//",
    },
  ];
  